Lesson 35.
第35课。
Justice was done.
正义完成了。
justice: n.   正义，公正；司法, court: n.   法院, law: n.   法律
The word justice is usually associated with courts of law.
正义一词通常与法院有关。
justice: n.   正义，公正；司法, innocence: n.   无辜
We might say that justice has been done when a man's innocence or guilt has been proved
我们可能会说，当一个人的纯真或罪恶感证明了正义
beyond doubt.
毫无疑问。
law: n.   法律
Justice is part of the complex machinery of the law.
正义是法律复杂机构的一部分。
undertake: v.   承担；着手做, arduous: adj. 艰苦的，艰难的
Those who seek it undertake an arduous journey and can never be sure that they will find
那些寻求它的人进行了艰苦的旅程，永远无法确定他们会发现
it.
它。
Judges.
法官。
However wise or eminent, our human and can make mistakes.
无论明智或杰出，我们的人都会犯错。
justice: n.   正义，公正；司法, abstract: adj. 抽象的
There are rare instances when justice almost ceases to be an abstract concept.
很少有正义几乎不再是一个抽象的概念。
interference: n.   干涉
Reward or punishment are meted out quite independent of human interference.
奖励或惩罚被完全独立于人类干扰。
justice: n.   正义，公正；司法
At such times, justice acts like a living force.
在这种时候，正义像活力。
When we use a phrase like, it serves him right.
当我们使用类似的短语时，它可以为他服务。
justice: n.   正义，公正；司法
We are, in part, admitting that a certain set of circumstances has enabled justice to
我们在某种程度上承认某种情况使正义能够
accord: n.   一致
act of its own accord.
自己的行为。
premises: n.    房屋
When a thief was caught on the premises of large jewelry store on morning, the shop
早上在大型珠宝店的场所捕获小偷时，商店
assistance must have found it impossible to resist the temptation to say, it serves him.
援助一定发现不可能抵制诱惑说，这为他服务。
convert: v.   转变，改变, disused: adj. 不再用的，废弃的, fireplace: n.   壁炉
Right, the shop was an old converted house with many large, disused fireplaces and tall
是的，这家商店是一间古老的房子
narrow chimneys.
狭窄的烟囱。
Towards midday, a girl heard a muffed cry coming from behind on of the walls.
截至中午，一个女孩听到墙壁后面的闷闷不乐的声音。
As the cry was repeated several times.
当哭声重复几次时。
She ran to tell the manager who promptly rang up the fire brigade.
她跑去告诉经理，后者迅速响起了消防队。
The cry had certainly come form one of the chimneys.
哭泣肯定是烟囱之一。
But as there were so many of them, the firefighters could not be certain which one it was.
但是，由于其中很多，消防员无法确定它是哪一个。
They located the right chimney by tapping at the walls and listening for the man's
他们通过敲击墙壁并聆听男人的烟囱找到了右烟囱
cries.
哭了。
chip: v.   砍，削，凿
After chipping through a wall which was 18 inches thick, they found that a man had been
在厚18英寸厚的墙壁后，他们发现一个人已经在
trapped in the chimney.
被困在烟囱中。
As it was extremely narrow.
因为它非常狭窄。
The man was unable to move.
该男子无法移动。
But the firefighters were eventually able to free him by cutting a huge hole in the wall.
但是消防员最终能够通过在墙上砍大巨大的洞来释放他。
The sorry looking.
对不起。
emerge: v.   （从某处）出现
Lackin figure that emerged.
缺乏出现的数字。
Admitted at once that he had tried to break into the shop during the night but had got stuck
立刻承认他试图在夜间闯入商店，但被卡住了
in the chimney.
在烟囱。
He had been there for nearly 10 hours.
他去过那里近10个小时。
Dys had been done even before the man was handed over to the police.
在该男子被移交给警察之前，DYS已经完成。